[{"answer": "Well, the damage to the show is they can't produce a show.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "I mean where is the damage to the show here from Charlie's behavior off screen?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Incredibly enough -- incredibly enough it does usually work.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "To replace them with somebody else?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Well, I think he is.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "Is Charlie Sheen employable anymore in television in America?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "With all due respect to your wonderful career and reality television, Piers, that's really the only thing that's left for Charlie Sheen right now.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "Do you think that Charlie is still bankable?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "I mean, Janice -- let me bring in, let me bring in Janice here because when Charlie sat here with me a week ago, actually, in one of the breaks, I said you're on Twitter.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "Charlie Sheen, who knows?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "Well, listen, I also think he's become a little bit of a folk hero to some people, you know, whether we like it or not.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "Isn't he?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "I don't --", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "Wouldn't yours be, Howard?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "In some form, probably yes.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Yes or no, Howard?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Within a year, I'd say yes.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Bill Carter?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Maybe on a reality show a year from now.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "And Steve?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "He's very nice.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "Is he nice?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "I have no comment on it.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "But what's your personal view of Charlie?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "I do, but I have no comment on the show about it.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "No view of him?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Well, I just think it would be -- it wouldn't be right for any of us to comment about it.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Not to us.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "You're called the talk ladies, aren't you?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "We haven't talked about it not once.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "None of you talked about Charlie Sheen?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "Well, I know you've talked about him.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Sharon is famous for going who?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "You want to take that or --", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "Does it really matter how somebody behaves in their private lives when it comes to the performance on a TV show?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "Yes, I think, speaking as a parent, you only want the best for your child.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "That's the hard bit, isn't it, for a parent when you have a child that's gone off the rails whatever age they are?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "No, he's about 44.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "He's not?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "He has, what, five kids?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "You should answer that because you do breaking news, Piers.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "I mean aren't our news values a bit warped?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "Well, no, actually.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "So it's about the ratings?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Well, you know, it's like I said.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "You know, is it right to castigate Charlie Sheen now again for alleged misdemeanors against women, for example?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Never.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "Have you not?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "I think like two times a week at least.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "It's unpredictable.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "I'm like, oh, what is Sharon going to do today?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Well, it was Sara's creation but I will say what I think makes our show work is that you have five very different women who are all smart and funny and honest and they're not afraid to speak the truth and speak their mind.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "I think that's a smart move but how did you come to decide the way you were going to take it?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "I would say the number one issue is probably marital problems, or just relationship problems.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "What's the one thing you think the viewers keep coming back to?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "More lashings of sex?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Or too much.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "Because they're getting not enough of it?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Sara, was that the concept you had originally?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "We think it's great.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "What do you all think of \"The View\"?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "I was on bed rest 13 years ago when \"The View\" started.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "I love it.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "Rivals?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "I think we have come a long way.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Talking?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "You're not allowed on the show.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "What does banning from in Britain?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 612, "question": "Me?", "qSentId": 611}, {"answer": "The best, the best.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "Do you think that was a prize?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "I keep it in my -- I have it in my -- where I keep my things.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "Where is the handbag?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "At dancing, singing.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 668, "question": "At what?", "qSentId": 667}, {"answer": "I wish we had.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "Do you have a piece of tape on that?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "That's what I was meant to be, failed.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "How can you say \"failed\" and \"prodigy\"?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "We should mention because our boss is here from -- there's ten days left and people want to be judged by us.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "Can you two continue this?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "It's a sad statement on humanity and we all love a train wreck, you know, and that's basically what it is.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 728, "question": "What life's like these days?", "qSentId": 727}, {"answer": "In the beginning I thought funny, some of the statements, \"Winner, duh,\" and all that.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 738, "question": "Do you find any of what Charlie's doing funny in a dark way?", "qSentId": 737}, {"answer": "More than 30 years.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 747, "question": "You have been in the business 30 years now?", "qSentId": 746}, {"answer": "How do you avoid going off the rails.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 762, "question": "The secret?", "qSentId": 761}, {"answer": "I still do 200 live shows a year.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 774, "question": "How many shows do you do a year?", "qSentId": 773}, {"answer": "America, Britain, Canada.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 776, "question": "All around America?", "qSentId": 775}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 785, "question": "You fly all around America?", "qSentId": 784}, {"answer": "I need to be home.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 787, "question": "But you like to come back, don't you?", "qSentId": 786}, {"answer": "You did.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 807, "question": "Who got you on twitter?", "qSentId": 806}, {"answer": "First and foremost, I have a loving family, my wife is a saint.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 839, "question": "How do you have to lead your life, given the condition that you have?", "qSentId": 838}, {"answer": "It's who I am.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 843, "question": "It's a fulltime thing for you?", "qSentId": 842}, {"answer": "Right after \"American Idol,\" Thursday, March 31st, on FOX.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 875, "question": "When does it air?", "qSentId": 874}, {"answer": "Not me.", "docId": "110307pmt", "aSentId": 877, "question": "You being annoying to people?", "qSentId": 876}]